RASHI SRIVASTAVA

Lead Product Manager

srashi1994@gmail.com • https://www.linkedin.com/in/srashi/

Summary

With ~7 years of experience in Product Management in start up environments, I bring the expertise in building the products from scratch and quiding the same through 0 to 1 journey with a strong metric & experiment driven approach.

Experience

Abu Dhabi Col earn

Lead Product Manager 09/2023 CoLearn is an e-learning solution, dedicated to empowering Indonesian students grades 4 to 12 by offering live classes for an enriched learning

- · Orchestrated the expansion of live classes from 1000 to over 5000 paid subscribers within a swift six-month period
- Achieved a remarkable 97% reduction in onboarding time by streamlining and automating the entire end-to-end process
- Slashed weekly support time by 60% via strategic implementation of crucial customer support data infrastructure and in-app support
- Boosted paid user engagement by 12% by experimentation with a range of in-class and post-class activities
- · Mentored promising team members across business teams & enabled their upward movement in Product by crafting different training programs

05/2021 - 08/2023 Senior Product Manager

Spearheaded growth from inception to over 1000 paid subscribers within one year

experience

- Amplified free to trial users sign ups by 5X within the initial three months using a strategic sequence of iterative A/B tests
- Increased user attendance to over 90% for approximately 75% of users, up from 58% by experiment with different instant gratification features
- Pioneered the development of a system to monitor in-class interactions, enabling the establishment of comprehensive engagement metrics and a performance index for teachers

Gurgaon **INDmoney**

Associate Product Manager 11/2020 - 04/2021

INDmoney is the super money app focused on Indian market which enables it's users to manage all your money at one place

- Developed the Loan Against Investments product vertical from inception
- Designed numerous marketing campaign experiments, conducting weekly A/B tests that resulted in a 40% surge in acquired leads
- Enhanced bank loan approval rates by 7% through the implementation of technology-driven and process-led adjustments

Delhi Ziploan

Associate Product Manager 07/2019 - 11/2020

Ziploan revolutionizes small business financing by providing tailored loan products and streamlined processes to empower MSMEs

- Increased application punches by ~23% via automation of Direct Selling Agents (DSA) Payout process as it helped improve DSA relations
- Reduced delinquency instances by 4% by designing an Early Warning Signal system
- Reduced credit approval rate by 3% by building a Credit Deviations & Approval's Risk Assessment model

Noida **Jsimple**

09/2017 - 07/2020 **Business Analyst**

Jsimple led the creation and rollout of Verko, a B2B SaaS Insurance & Employee Management tool, in partnership with Employee Family Protection Inc, used by major US-based Fortune 500 insurance companies including Cigna, United Healthcare Group, and Rose and Kiernan.

- Enhanced quarterly sales by 18% via the implementation of an insurance recommendation feature
- Automated invoice generation, reducing manual effort by 60%, by developing a billing tool for employers and insurance providers

Education

Noida **Amity University** Btech Information Technology

06/2013 - 07/2017

References

Sandeep Devram — Chief Product Officer & CoFounder, CoLearn

Aram Bhusal — Head of Engineering, Consolidate Health

Ishita Parbat — Senior Product Management Leader, Grab